So this word is ear, which means this word is beer.
No, it's beer, you know what I'm saying?
It's because it's ear with a B.
Bear, that's why.
Which means this word would be?
Bear?
No, what would you think?
It's bear with a D.
Beard.
Let's take a step back, okay.
This word is bear, which means this word is
fair.
No, it's fear.
You know what I'm saying?
Ear with an F out here, which means
ear with a P would be pier.
No, it's pear.
Remember bear?
I guess I'm moving too fast.
So ear with an H would be pier?
No, here.
And then if you add a D,
here, no, it's heard.
No, it's wrong.
It's here with a D.
Herd, which means this word would be?
Herd.
No, it's heart.
Why do you think?
Here with a T, heart, you know what I'm saying?
No, okay.